parentpalace.com 2011-12-28

# Privacy Policy - Parent Palace

Privacy Policy for parentpalace.com

The privacy of our visitors to parentpalace.com is important to us.

At parentpalace.com, we recognize that privacy of your personal information is  
important. Here is information on what types of personal information we receive  
and collect when you use and visit parentpalace.com, and how we safeguard your  
information.  We never sell your personal information to third parties.

Log Files  
As with most other websites, we collect and use the data  
contained in log files.  The information in the log files include  your IP  
(internet protocol) address, your ISP (internet service provider, such as AOL or  
Shaw Cable), the browser you used to visit our site (such as Internet Explorer  
or Firefox), the time you visited our site and which pages you visited  
throughout our site.

Cookies and Web Beacons  
We do use cookies to store information, such as  
your personal preferences when you visit our site.  This could include only  
showing you a popup once in your visit, or the ability to login to some of our  
features, such as forums.

We also use third party advertisements on parentpalace.com to support our site.  Some  
of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when  
they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers (such as  
Google through the Google AdSense program) information including your IP  
address, your ISP , the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases,  
whether you have Flash installed.  This is generally used for geotargeting  
purposes (showing New York real estate ads to someone in New York, for example)  
or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited (such as showing cooking  
ads to someone who frequents cooking sites).

You can chose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party  
cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs such as  
Norton Internet Security.  However, this can affect how you are able to interact  
with our site as well as other websites.  This could include the inability to  
login to services or programs, such as logging into forums or accounts.
